# **GOODNESS ARINZE OKAFOR**

Goodnessokafor462@gmail.com +2347010424178

### 3 Years of Administrative Experience

With over Two (2) Years of Administrative Experience and One (1) Year of Office duty As an Administrative Secretary in the Nigeria Uyo Mission of the church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day saint, I have cultivated a passion for Administrative duties and competence. During my service as an administrative secretary, I worked diligently in fulfilling my duties. I was known for my innovative and indefatigable spirit, as part of my accomplishments I created a system format that helped reduced the work load and made the organization of employee's information easy. I believe my expertise will be of great benefit to your Organization.

### Skills

- Advanced knowledge of Microsoft Office
- Fluent in Speaking and Writing the English language
- knowledge of Python, HTML and CSS
- Compliant and disciplined

- Perspicacious
- Innovative
- Punctual
- inclusive

# Experience

# Administrative Secretary Nigeria Uyo Mission

April 2021- June 2022

- Received and sent Official missions' correspondence promptly, leading to accurate circulation of information.
- Organized an inventory system that helped reduced the misplacement of items by 38%.
- Created an online database that helped in accessing missionary's information in any location and at any given time.
- Organized over 100 successful flights arrangements for incoming and outgoing missionaries.

### Customer Attendant/Cashier Simco tech Multi Synergy

Dec 2018- Jun 2020

- Resolved 88% of customer related issues, increasing customers trust and increasing sales.
- Successfully delivered 98.9% of customers' orders with less than 2% casualties.
- Accurately documents all sales records with no recorded cash shortage.

## Education

Brigham Young University Idaho(online) worldwide

April 2022 - Current

#### **High School Leaving Certificate**

Government Science Secondary School Tungan Maje.

Sep 2012 - aug 2016